Guide to the North Carolina Farm Bureau Records
North Carolina Farm Bureau Records
- Financial Materials, 1940-1989; 7 linear feet
  - Reference Materials and Reports, 1965-1999; 8 linear feet
    - United States Department of Agriculture Reports
      - Supply and Demand Estimates, January - June 1997 (Box 63, Folder 4)
      - Supply and Demand Estimates, July - December 1997 (Box 63, Folder 5)
      - Supply and Demand Estimates, January - June 1998 (Box 63, Folder 6)
      - Supply and Demand Estimates, July - December 1998 (Box 63, Folder 7)
      - Tobacco Stocks, 1978 - 1984 (Box 63, Folder 8)
      - Tobacco Stocks, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 9)
      - Wheat, 1992 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - American Farm Bureau Federation Publications
      - Commodity Reports, December 1993 - February 1994 (Box 64, Folder 1)
      - Commodity Reports, March 1994 (Box 64, Folder 2)
      - Commodity Reports, April - May 1994 (Box 64, Folder 3)
      - Executive News Watch, October 1994 (Box 64, Folder 4)
      - Executive News Watch, November 1994 (Box 64, Folder 5)
      - Executive News Watch, December 1994 (Box 64, Folder 6)
      - Executive News Watch, January 1995 (Box 64, Folder 7)
      - Executive News Watch, February 1995 (Box 64, Folder 8)
      - Executive News Watch, March 1995 (Box 64, Folder 9)
      - Executive News Watch, April 1995 (Box 64, Folder 10)
      - Executive News Watch, May 1995 (Box 64, Folder 11)
      - Executive News Watch, June 1995 (Box 64, Folder 12)
      - Executive News Watch, June 1996 (Box 64, Folder 13)
      - Executive News Watch, April 1997 (Box 64, Folder 14)
      - Executive News Watch, May 1997 (Box 64, Folder 15)
      - Executive News Watch, June 1997 (Box 64, Folder 16)
      - Executive News Watch, July 1997 (Box 64, Folder 17)
      - Executive News Watch, August 1997 (Box 64, Folder 18)
      - Executive News Watch, September 1997 (Box 64, Folder 19)
      - Executive News Watch, October 1997 (Box 64, Folder 20)
      - Executive News Watch, November 1997 (Box 64, Folder 21)
      - Executive News Watch, December 1997 (Box 64, Folder 22)
      - Executive News Watch, January 1998 (Box 65, Folder 1)
      - Executive News Watch, February 1998 (Box 65, Folder 2)
      - Executive News Watch, March 1998 (Box 65, Folder 3)
      - Executive News Watch, April 1998 (Box 65, Folder 4)
      - Executive News Watch, May 1998 (Box 65, Folder 5)
      - Executive News Watch, June 1998 (Box 65, Folder 6)
      - Executive News Watch, July 1998 (Box 65, Folder 7)
      - Executive News Watch, August 1998 (Box 65, Folder 8)
      - Executive News Watch, September 1998 (Box 65, Folder 9)
      - Executive News Watch, October 1998 (Box 65, Folder 10)
      - Executive News Watch, November 1998 (Box 65, Folder 11)
      - Executive News Watch, December 1998 (Box 65, Folder 12)
      - Executive News Watch, January 1999 (Box 65, Folder 13)
      - Executive News Watch, February 1999 (Box 65, Folder 14)
      - Executive News Watch, March 1999 (Box 65, Folder 15)
      - Executive News Watch, April 1999 (Box 65, Folder 16)
      - Executive News Watch, May 1999 (Box 65, Folder 17)
      - Executive News Watch, June 1999 (Box 65, Folder 18)
      - Executive News Watch, July 1999 (Box 65, Folder 19)
      - ACRES, General Program Information (Box 66, Folder 1)
      - ACRES, General Program Information (Box 66, Folder 2)
      - ACRES, General Program Information (Box 66, Folder 3)
      - ACRES Reports, 1986 - 1989 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - North Carolina Department of Agriculture Publications
      - Biotechnology, January - August 1993 (Box 66, Folder 5)
      - Biotechnology, September - December 1993 (Box 66, Folder 6)
      - Biotechnology, April - July 1994 (Box 66, Folder 7)
      - Biotechnology, August - December 1994 (Box 66, Folder 8)
      - Biotechnology, 1995 (Box 66, Folder 9)
      - Broilers, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 1)
      - Broilers, 1994 (Box 67, Folder 2)
      - Broilers, 1995 - 1996 (Box 67, Folder 3)
      - Crops, 1992 - 1997 (Box 67, Folder 4)
      - Farms, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 5)
      - Farms, January - June 1994 (Box 67, Folder 6)
      - Farms, July - December 1994 (Box 67, Folder 7)
      - Farms, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 8)
      - Grain Market, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 9)
      - Livestock Market, 1995 - 1996 (Box 67, Folder 10)
      - News, 1994 (Box 67, Folder 11)
      - News, 1995 - 1997 (Box 67, Folder 12)
      - Poultry News, 1996 - 1999 (Box 67, Folder 13)
      - Sweet Potato Market, 1995 - 1996 (Box 67, Folder 14)
      - Weather and Crops, 1994 (Box 67, Folder 15)
      - Weather and Crops, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 16)
      - Weather and Crops, 1996 (Box 67, Folder 17)
      - Weather and Crops, 1997 (Box 67, Folder 18)
      - Weather and Crops, 1997 (Box 67, Folder 19)
      - Weather and Crops, 1998 (Box 67, Folder 20)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 67, Folder 21)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 67, Folder 22)
    - Federal Register
      - 1980 (Box 68, Folder 1)
      - 1981 (Box 68, Folder 2)
      - 1982 (Box 68, Folder 3)
      - 1983 (Box 68, Folder 4)
      - 1984 (Box 68, Folder 5)
      - 1985 (Box 68, Folder 6)
      - 1986 (Box 68, Folder 7)
      - 1987 (Box 68, Folder 8)
      - 1988 (Box 68, Folder 9)
      - 1989 (Box 68, Folder 10)
      - 1990 (Box 68, Folder 11)
      - 1991 (Box 68, Folder 12)
      - July - August 1992 (Box 68, Folder 13)
      - September - October 1992 (Box 68, Folder 14)
      - November - December 1992 (Box 68, Folder 15)
      - January - March 1993 (Box 68, Folder 16)
      - April - June 1993 (Box 68, Folder 17)
      - July - September 1993 (Box 68, Folder 18)
      - October - December 1993 (Box 68, Folder 19)
      - January - February, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 1)
      - March - April, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 2)
      - September - October, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 3)
      - November, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 4)
      - December, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 5)
      - 1995 (Box 69, Folder 6)
      - 1998 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Kiplinger Agricultural Letters
      - 1992 - 1993 (Box 69, Folder 8)
      - 1994 - 1995 (Box 69, Folder 9)
      - 1996 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - DTN Reports
      - April - May 1995 (Box 69, Folder 11)
      - June 1995 (Box 69, Folder 12)
      - July 1995 (Box 69, Folder 13)
      - August 1995 (Box 69, Folder 14)
      - September 1995 (Box 69, Folder 15)
      - October 1995 (Box 69, Folder 16)
      - November 1995 (Box 69, Folder 17)
      - December 1995 (Box 69, Folder 18)
      - January 1996 (Box 70, Folder 1)
      - February 1996 (Box 70, Folder 2)
      - March 1996 (Box 70, Folder 3)
      - April - May 1996 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Public Policy, Trade, and Census Information, 1980s-1990s
      - Public Policy, Trade, and Agricultural Census Material, 1980s-1990s (Carton 92)
      - Conservation Provisions and Reference Material, 1980s-1990s (Carton 94)
      - Animal Rights Activism Reference Material, 1980s-1990s (Carton 94)
      - Conservation and Proctection Policies and Reference Material, 1970s-1990s (Carton 95)
    - Organizational Associations Reference Materials, 1960s-1990s
      - Organizational Associations, 1960s-1980s (Carton 93)
      - General Organizational Refernece Material, 19980s-1990s (Carton 94)
      - Cooperatives Inforamtion and Cooperative Agreements, 1960s-1980s (Carton 94)
      - Committee Minutes, 1990s (Carton 94)
    - Mixed Crop Reference Materials and Publications, 1970s-1990s
      - Crop Reference Material, 1990s (Carton 93)
      - Crop Reference Material, 1970s-1990s (Carton 94)
      - Crops and Commodities Reference Material, 1980s-1990s (Carton 95)
    - Peanut Newsletters, Committee Minutes and Reference Materials, 1980s-1990s
      - Peanut Farmer, February - April, 1990 (Box 71, Folder 15)
      - Peanut Farmer, May 1990 - January, 1991 (Box 71, Folder 16)
      - Peanut News, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 17)
      - Peanut News, 1993 (Box 71, Folder 18)
      - Peanut Report, 1993 (Box 71, Folder 19)
      - Peanut Report, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 20)
      - Peanut Reference Material, 1980s-1990s (Carton 91)
      - Peanut Reference Material, 1990s (Carton 92)
      - Peanut Reference Material, 1990s (Carton 93)
      - Peanut Reference Material, 1990s (Carton 94)
      - Peanut Reference Material, 1990s (Carton 95)
    - Tobacco Newsletters, Publications, and Reference Materials, 1970s-1990s
      - Tobacco Associates- General Information (Box 72, Folder 1)
      - Tobacco Associates- Newsletters, 1986-1990 (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - Tobacco Associates- Annual Reports, 1971-1976 (Box 72, Folder 3)
      - Tobacco Associates- Annual Reports, 1977-1983 (Box 72, Folder 4)
      - Tobacco Associates- Annual Reports, 1984-1987 (Box 72, Folder 5)
      - Tobacco Associates- Annual Reports, 1988-1991 (Box 72, Folder 6)
      - North Carolina Tobacco Growers Association- General Information (Box 72, Folder 7)
      - North Carolina Tobacco Growers Association- General Information (Box 72, Folder 8)
      - North Carolina Tobacco Growers Association- Resolutions (Box 72, Folder 9)
      - North Carolina Tobacco Growers Association- Newsletters (Box 72, Folder 10)
      - Flue-Cured Tobacco Cooperative- Bylaws (Box 72, Folder 11)
      - Flue-Cured Tobacco Cooperative- Investigations (Box 72, Folder 12)
      - Flue-Cured Tobacco Cooperative- Investigations (Box 72, Folder 13)
      - American Tobacco Grower, 1990 - 1991 (Box 73, Folder 1)
      - Cigarette Tax Report, 1984 (Box 73, Folder 2)
      - Cigarette Tax Report, 1985 (Box 73, Folder 3)
      - Cigarette Tax Report, 1986- 1988 (Box 73, Folder 4)
      - Tobacco Farmer, January - March 1989 (Box 73, Folder 5)
      - Tobacco Farmer, April - June 1989 (Box 73, Folder 6)
      - Tobacco Farmer, November - December 1989 (Box 73, Folder 7)
      - Tobacco Farmer, January - March 1990 (Box 73, Folder 8)
      - Tobacco Farmer, April - December 1990 (Box 73, Folder 9)
      - Tobacco Farmer, 1991 (Box 73, Folder 10)
      - Tobacco Grower, 1984 - 1985 (Box 73, Folder 11)
      - Stabilization Newsletter, 1986 (Box 73, Folder 12)
      - Stabilization Newsletter, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 13)
      - Stabilization Newsletter, 1988 (Box 73, Folder 14)
      - Stabilization Newsletter, 1989 (Box 73, Folder 15)
      - Stabilization Newsletter, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 16)
      - Stabilization Newsletter, 1991 (Box 73, Folder 17)
      - Stabilization Newsletter, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 18)
      - Tobacco Legislation and Information, 1970s-1980s (Carton 89)
      - Domestic and International Tobacco, 1980s (Carton 90)
      - Tobacco Reference Material, 1980s-1990s (Carton 93)
    - Livestock Newsletters, Minutes, Legislations and Reference Materials, 1980s-1990s
      - Livestock Reference Material, 1980s-1990s (Carton 91)
      - Livestock Reference Material, 1990s (Carton 93)
      - Livestock Reference Material, 1980s-1990s (Carton 94)
      - Livestock Reference Material, 1990s (Carton 95)
- Photographs and Scrapbooks, 1958-1993; 0.5 linear feet
  The photograph series is split into two subseries. The first of these is comprised of black and white prints of various Farm Bureau leaders and buildings. The second subseries of the photograph collection contains two scrapbooks compiled by the North Carolina Farm Bureau for the years 1958-1959 and 1959-1960. These scrapbooks include black and white photographs taken at various Farm Bureau events as well as newspaper articles citing the organization.
  - Photographic Prints
    - North Carolina Farm Bureau Presidents
      - A.C. Edwards (Box 74, Folder 1)
      - B.C. Mangum (Box 74, Folder 2)
      - P.N. Taylor (Box 74, Folder 3)
      - J.E. Winslow (Box 74, Folder 4)
      - Larry Wooten, President of North Carolina Farm Bureau (Box 103, Folder 6)
      - Photographs, Feb-96 (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - General North Carolina Farm Bureau Photographs
      - Farm Bureau Buildings (Box 74, Folder 5)
      - Farm Bureau Buildings (Box 104, Folder 1)
      - Farm Bureau Meetings (Box 74, Folder 6)
      - North Carolina Farmers and Farmland, photographs from the Paul Shackelford Papers, 1968-1971 (Box 104, Folder 2)
      - North Carolina Farmland and Farmers (Box 74, Folder 7)
      - Photographs 1: Press photographs and meetings, circa 1950-1980 (Box 96, Folder 1)
      - Photographs 2, circa 1950-1970 (Box 96, Folder 2)
      - Photographs 3, circa 1950-1970 (Box 96, Folder 3)
      - Photographs 4, circa 1950-1970 (Box 96, Folder 4)
      - Photographs 5, circa 1950-1970 (Box 96, Folder 5)
      - Photographs 6: Annual meeting, organization conference, television broadcast, Franklin County Farm Bureau, tobacco images, circa 1950-1970 (Box 97, Folder 1)
      - Photographs 7: Office images, portraits, annual meeting, circa 1950-1970 (Box 97, Folder 2)
      - Photographs 8: Annual convention, portraits, Mercer County Farm Bureau office, promotional and press photos, circa 1950-1970 (Box 97, Folder 3)
      - Photographs 9: Annual meeting, press photographs/farm photographs, many late 1970s, circa 1950-1970 (Box 97, Folder 4)
      - Photographs 10: Group hotographs, agricultural photographs, circa 1950-1970 (Box 97, Folder 5)
      - Photographs 11: Annual meeting, portraits, group photos, circa 1950-1970 (Box 97, Folder 6)
      - Photographs 12: Irby Walker, circa 1950-1970 (Box 98, Folder 1)
      - Photographs 13, circa 1950-1990 (Box 98, Folder 2)
      - Photographs 14: Mostly promotional photographs of agriculture and crafts with some portraits and group photographs, circa 1950-1980 (Box 98, Folder 3)
      - Photographs 15: Women's Committee, circa 1950-1980 (Box 98, Folder 4)
      - Photographs 16: John Sledge and B. C. Mangum, circa 1950-1970 (Box 98, Folder 5)
      - Photographs 17: Awards, memorial service, youth exchange students, several office and promotional photographs, includes one "Nickels for Know-How" program originally stored with the photographs, circa 1950-1970 (Box 99, Folder 1)
      - Photographs 18: Group photographs, Safemark tire promotional photos, annual meeting photos, county office and county event photos, photographs with female ambassador from India, circa 1950-1970 (Box 99, Folder 2)
      - Photographs 19: New building on Glenwood, American Farm Bureau Federation annual meeting, various group and promotional photographs, circa 1950-1970 (Box 99, Folder 3)
      - Photographs 20: 50th anniversary photographs, women in Farm Bureau, home demonstration clubs delegates, various convention and meeting photographs and awards, circa 1950-1970 (Box 99, Folder 4)
      - Photographs 21, including agricultural and tobacco photographs, circa 1950-1980 (Box 100, Folder 7)
      - Photographs 23: Agricultural photographs, group hotographs, portraits, circa 1950-1980 (Box 100, Folder 8)
      - Photographs 24: Agricultural photographs, agricultural labs, portraits, pageant photographs, Washington, D.C., circa 1950-1980 (Box 101, Folder 1)
      - Photographs 25: Agricultural photographs, agricultural labs, portraits, American Farm Bureau Federation Convention, circa 1950-1980 (Box 101, Folder 2)
      - Photographs 26, including 50th anniversary of American Farm Bureau Federation and various agricultural photographs, some North Carolina State University photographs, circa 1950-1980 (Box 101, Folder 3)
      - Photographs and Slides, 1981 (Box 100, Folder 1)
      - Photographs and Slides, 1982 (Box 100, Folder 2)
      - Photographs and Slides, 1983 (Box 100, Folder 3)
      - Slides, 1985 (Box 100, Folder 4)
      - Slides, 1986 (Box 100, Folder 5)
      - Slides, 1987 (Box 100, Folder 6)
      - Photographs, including 57th North Carolina Farm Bureau Annual Meeting, 1980s-1990s (Box 101, Folder 5)
      - Photographs: Portraits (Box 102, Folder 1)
      - Photographs: Groundbreaking for oak tree, holiday and promotional photographs, 1990s (Box 102, Folder 2)
      - Photographs, including photographs of Glenwood Avenue building (Box 102, Folder 3)
      - Photographs, including "fashion show," and North Carolina Farm Bureau supports blueberry growers, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 102, Folder 4)
      - Photographs, primarily group photographs and women, circa 1950-1980 (Box 102, Folder 5)
      - Photographs, 27 including North Carolina Farm Bureau county representatives, American Farm Bureau Federation Officers and board of directors (1964), awards, and group photographs, circa 1950-1970 (Box 102, Folder 6)
      - Photographs, including Jones County Farm Bureau and Youth Power, circa 1940-1960 (Box 103, Folder 1)
      - Photographs, circa 1940-1970 (Box 103, Folder 2)
      - State Board and County Presidents, 2004-2006 (Box 103, Folder 3)
      - Administration, North Carolina Farm Bureau State Board of Directors, 1980s-1990s (Box 103, Folder 4)
      - North Carolina Farm Bureau Administration, including signed photograph from Governor Jim Martin to Mr. William "Billy" Upchurch, between 1985 and 1993 (Box 103, Folder 5)
      - North Carolina Farm Bureau Meetings (Box 104, Folder 3)
      - Organizational Groups (Box 104, Folder 4)
      - Organizational Groups, IFAL (Box 104, Folder 5)
      - North Carolina Farm Bureau Awards (Box 104, Folder 6)
      - Photographs, unidentified, circa 1990s (Box 104, Folder 7)
      - Photographs, 1995, April 1995 (Box 105, Folder 1)
      - Photographs, 1995, May 1995 (Box 105, Folder 2)
      - Photographs, 1995, June 1995 (Box 105, Folder 3)
      - Photographs, 1995, July-August 1995 (Box 105, Folder 4)
      - Photographs, 1995, September 1995 (Box 105, Folder 5)
      - Photographs, 1995, October 1995 (Box 105, Folder 6)
      - Photographs, Nov-95 (Box 105, Folder 7)
      - Photographs, Dec-95 (Box 105, Folder 6)
      - Photographs, Jan-96 (Box 106, Folder 7)
      - Photographs, Mar-96 (Box 106, Folder 2)
      - Photographs, Apr-96 (Box 106, Folder 3)
      - Photographs, May-96 (Box 106, Folder 4)
      - Photographs, Jun-96 (Box 106, Folder 5)
      - Photographs, July-August (Box 106, Folder 6)
      - Photographs, Sep-96 (Box 106, Folder 7)
      - Photographs, Oct-96 (Box 106, Folder 8)
      - Photographs, Nov-96 (Box 106, Folder 9)
      - Photographs, Dec-96 (Box 106, Folder 10)
      - Photographs, Jan-97 (Box 107, Folder 1)
      - Photographs, Feb-97 (Box 107, Folder 2)
      - Photographs, Mar-97 (Box 107, Folder 3)
      - Photographs, Apr-97 (Box 107, Folder 4)
      - Photographs, May-97 (Box 107, Folder 5)
      - Photographs, Jun-97 (Box 107, Folder 6)
      - Photographs, July-August 1997 (Box 107, Folder 7)
      - Photographs, Sep-97 (Box 107, Folder 8)
      - Photographs, Oct-97 (Box 107, Folder 9)
      - Photographs, Nov-97 (Box 107, Folder 10)
      - Photographs, Dec-97 (Box 107, Folder 11)
      - Photographs, Jan-98 (Box 108, Folder 1)
      - Photographs, Feb-98 (Box 108, Folder 2)
      - Photographs, Mar-98 (Box 108, Folder 3)
      - Photographs, Apr-98 (Box 108, Folder 4)
      - Photographs, May-98 (Box 108, Folder 5)
      - Photographs, Jun-98 (Box 108, Folder 6)
      - Photographs, July-August 1998 (Box 108, Folder 7)
      - Photographs, Sep-98 (Box 108, Folder 9)
      - Photographs, Oct-98 (Box 108, Folder 10)
      - Photographs, Nov-98 (Box 108, Folder 11)
      - Photographs, Dec-98 (Box 109, Folder 1)
      - Photographs, Jan-99 (Box 109, Folder 2)
      - Photographs, Feb-99 (Box 109, Folder 3)
      - Photographs, Mar-99 (Box 109, Folder 4)
      - Photographs, Apr-99 (Box 109, Folder 5)
      - Photographs, May-99 (Box 109, Folder 6)
      - Photographs, Jun-99 (Box 109, Folder 7)
      - Photographs, July-August 1999 (Box 109, Folder 8)
      - Photographs, Sep-99 (Box 109, Folder 10)
      - Photographs, Oct-99 (Box 109, Folder 11)
      - Photographs, Nov-99 (Box 109, Folder 12)
      - Photographs, Dec-99 (Box 109, Folder 13)
      - Photographs, Dec-01 (Box 110, Folder 1)
      - Photographs, Dec-01 (Box 110, Folder 2)
      - Photographs, Feb-02 (Box 110, Folder 3)
      - Photographs, Mar-02 (Box 110, Folder 4)
      - Information Day, 1994 (Box 110, Folder 5)
      - Photographs, May-02 (Box 110, Folder 6)
      - Photographs, October/November 2002 (Box 110, Folder 7)
      - North Carolina Farm Bureau Headquarters, 12/1/2002 (Box 110, Folder 8)
      - Photographs, Mar-03 (Box 111, Folder 1)
      - Photographs, Apr-03 (Box 111, Folder 2)
      - Photographs, May-03 (Box 111, Folder 3)
      - Photographs, Jun-03 (Box 111, Folder 4)
      - Photographs, Aug-03 (Box 111, Folder 5)
      - Photographs, Sep-03 (Box 111, Folder 6)
      - Photographs, Oct-03 (Box 111, Folder 7)
      - Photographs, Nov-03 (Box 112, Folder 1)
      - Photographs, Dec-03 (Box 112, Folder 2)
      - Photographs, Feb-04 (Box 112, Folder 3)
      - Photographs, Mar-04 (Box 112, Folder 4)
      - Photographs, Apr-04 (Box 112, Folder 5)
      - Photographs, Jun-04 (Box 112, Folder 6)
      - Member Portraits (Box 128, Folder 2)
      - Photographs, Portraits and Group Photographs(1 of 3), circa 1930s-1980s (Box 128, Folder 3)
      - Photographs, Portraits and Group Photographs(2 of 3), circa 1930s-1980s (Box 128, Folder 4)
      - Photographs, Portraits and Group Photographs (3 of 3), circa 1930s-1980s (Box 128, Folder 5)
      - Slides (1 of 5) (Box 134, Folder 1)
      - Slides (2 of 5) (Box 134, Folder 2)
      - Slides (3 of 5) (Box 134, Folder 3)
      - Slides(4 of 5) (Box 134, Folder 4)
      - Slides (5 of 5) (Box 134, Folder 5)
      - Negatives, 1967-1970s (Box 135, Folder 2)
      - Negatives, 1967-1970s (Box 134, Folder 8)
      - Negatives, 1990s, unknown dates (Box 134, Folder 6)
      - Negatives, 1990s (Box 135, Folder 1)
      - Negatives, unknown date (Box 134, Folder 7)
      - Negatives, 2001 (Box 134, Folder 9)
      - Negatives, 2001 (Box 135, Folder 4)
      - Negatives, 2002 (Box 135, Folder 5)
      - Negatives, 2003 (Box 134, Folder 10)
      - Negatives, 2003 (Box 135, Folder 5)
      - Negatives, 2004 (Box 134, Folder 11)
      - Negatives, 2004 (Box 135, Folder 6)
      - Negatives, 2005 (Box 134, Folder 12)
      - Negatives, unknown dates, later 2000s (Box 134, Folder 13)
      - Negatives, late 2000s (Box 135, Folder 7)
      - Negatives, unknown dates (Box 135, Folder 2)
      - Promotional materials, signed photographs from youth program, Farm Bureau flag (Box 139)
      - Slide carousel, new employee orientation, 1991 (Halfbox 144)
      - Photographs, including 56th North Carolina Farm Bureau Annual Meeting, 1980s-1990s (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Scrapbooks
    - 1958 - 1959 (Flatbox 75, Folder 1)
    - 1959 - 1960 (Flatbox 76, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook, 1957 (Box 137)
    - Scrapbook pages, circa 1940-1950s (Box 138)
    - Scrapbook, 1955 (Box 141)
    - Oversized photographs, records, and scrapbook, circa 1950s (Box 142)
    - Scrapbook, January 1947- (Box 143)
    - 2 scrapbooks, 1940-1950 (Box 140)
- Audiovisual Materials, 1960-1999; 3.5 linear feet
  The audiovisual series contains a sound recording performed for the Farm Bureau by the Purdue University Marching Band, and film reels and videocassettes on various agricultural issues.
  - Film Reels
    - Unlabeled Reel from Orange County Farm Bureau (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Unlabeled Reel from Harnett County Farm Bureau (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Unlabeled Reel from Hertford County Farm Bureau (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Unlabeled Reel from Hertford County Farm Bureau (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Unlabeled Reel from Elizabeth City Farm Bureau (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - "The Formula for Success" (2 Copies) (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - "The Road to Delano" (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - "Rural Crime: They're Stealin' the Farm" (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Sound Recording
    - "The Spirit of Farm Bureau," performed by the Purdue University Marching Band (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Videocassettes
    - "Swine Handling and Transportation" (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - "Georgia Egg Commission" (Box 81, Folder 2)